Thank you for watching!
The members face off with their favorite easy-to-prepare evening meal!
Who will be crowned tonight's Meshitero Queen?
Here are the five entrants in the “Late-night but rice dishes” category!
Good night!
Wasn't there a lot of persimmons?
Persimmons were amazing!
No, no, no. It was really weird before.
It was edible.
But it's a light meal.
I don't cook at all, so I didn't have anything to put on it.
That one treasure...
Oh, you're the only one who has it?
It's all I have.
It's the only thing I've kept.
Don't worry, that hand is a rice ball.
It's not a rice ball.
I'm sure he's holding it, but it's okay.
What about Kaede Sato?
The image of her being clumsy comes first.
That's right.
I don't think I have much of an image.
I'm going to be covered in powder.
I don't know what you cook, but it looks like it's going to be covered in powder.
It's true that after cooking, I'm soaked.
But the food tastes good.
It's all wet.
Yumiki is so efficient. He cooks in no time.
I get the impression he's good at it.
I don't know... he's just an idiot.
She's got style.
She's energetic and pretty.
And yet she's stupid.
Dawn.
Zoon.
She's cute.
She has a long neck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Zoon is cute.
First of all, what is the rice dish for anxious Sato at hand?
I'll make it with a koukun.
Yes, sir!
It's a simple Korean-style rice bowl!
Oh, one more thing!
This is for us airmen!
We are aviators!
Thank you very much.
Well, it's made with sausage.
Aviation has a strong flavor.
Well, that's a little messy, but I think we've already got a pile of gloves out there.
Let's see.
I'm sure that's what they're like.
I'm counting on you.
See you at the Cooking Studio, Mr. Himura-san.
Yes, yes.
Now we're into the rice dishes.
I'm looking forward to it.
Sorry I just kicked your foot off.
No, no, no.
It's four eggs.
First of all, four eggs, stirred in a bowl.
What do you mean, “stirred”?
Lightly sugared.
It's like a sweet omelet.
Crumble eggs.
You've got three cups.
I don't care if it's a little bit of radish or not, it doesn't matter how much.
I don't think it matters how much.
Cut it into small pieces.
The excitement is to divide it into small portions.
So you cut it into small pieces?
Yes, crunchy, crunchy, crunchy texture
texture
Not cut
Not cutUncut.
Anything is good.
Nothing's good.
Nothing's too good to be true.
Nothing's good
Anything's good.
Then I fry the eggs in sesame oil and transfer them to a plate
You're doing it with your hands!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Aaaaah!
Woah, woah, woah...
There it is!
Brown sugar is sifting through.
Hot, hot, hot, hot.
Hot, hot, hot, hot. Red, red, red, red.
Still not sticking, still not sticking, still not sticking, still not sticking, still not sticking.
It still doesn't stick.
It's not burned yet, it's still got a little egg and other crumbs...
It's dirty.
I'll fry it.
Ko-kun, I'll fry it up.
Ko-kun, I'll fry them up
Mr. Kimura, when I look at it from this side, there's something beautiful like a dragon.
What's that dragon thing?
Is this it?
Serve rice.
Rice!
It's fine as it is.
Why can't we just leave it as it is?
It's not fine as it is.
We want you to take good care of Takashi.
I'm frying it now.
I'm frying them now.
I stir-fried Takashi.
Scrambled eggs, kimchi, and a bowl of rice.
Yes, it's fine as it is.
This is Korean seaweed flakes.These are Korean seaweed flakes.
You know, they sell those, right?
Yes, we sell them, so put this in the middle.
Finally, mayonnaise.
Mayonnaise.
Late-night mayonnaise.
It's perfect.
This is amazing.
What's the title?
It's a simple Korean-style rice bowl.
Here it is!
The aroma is fantastic!
Mix it.
Mix it?
You messed it up.
Yes, I did.
Ichimba style.
This is... this is good.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It smells so good!
Bon appétit!
This is absolutely delicious.
I'm sure it's good.
It's exactly what I imagine it tastes like.
It's so good!
Everyone loves this.
All of it.
The glue is good.
Everything is good, right?
I love the sweet egg.
It's got a real Korean flair.
Yes, it does.
It's good.
I would love to have some kind of seaweed soup with this.
Alone.
Yum!
Next, Yumiki's favorite rice dish!Next, Yumiki's favorite rice dish.
I'm going to nourish you with soybean flour!
I don't know what that means.
It's a rice dish, isn't it?
I was thinking of making furikake (sprinkles) with soybean flour.
Kinako furikake?
I have a secret ingredient.
It's a secret ingredient.
I have a hidden gem from a place I don't want to eat.
Hidden in the armpit.
What's that?
I have a hidden gem... and you can look forward to it.
I've got a hidden gem.
There's a hidden gem in the armpit.
Okay, Mr. Himura.
Okay, Miki!
First, the powdered dried sardines.
The powdered dried sardines.
Fish meal.
1 piece
1 cup
And then 1 piece of soybean flour like this.
Looks delicious!
1 done!
And finally, ground sesame seeds.
Yes, ground sesame!
Oh!
One.
All 1
Why do you insist on saying “one”?
And then almonds.
Why do you insist on saying one?
Can I have more?
Why are you speaking English now?
What?
Eezy-ska.
I'm sorry...Excuse me.
Almonds, please.
Almonds.
I went all out today.
I'm going all out.
One.
Two.
Three. - Three.
Four. - Four.
eggplant or its
remain
yes
I got one almond in there.
Yah!
Next, bonito flakes.
I just said “them”...
I just said “them”.
There are those guys...
Next is “katsuobushi”.
About this much.
About a pinch.
A little much.
Oh, no.
And this.
What's with that obsession?
And about this much.
After you crush this.
Put all the ingredients in a mortar and pestle.
Mash all the ingredients well.
Do you cook a lot?
I cook a lot.
I cook in the morning.
I cook lunch too.
You don't cook at night?
No, I don't.
I heard something I shouldn't have.I heard something I shouldn't have.
What do you mean?
Yes, well, it's done.
Here it is.
It's pretty shattered.
Is it done?
No, here.
You're going to sow it in the garden, right?
No, sir.
Get up.
Catch this bird and eat it.
No, sir.
I put it in the frying pan.
The finely milled ingredients are not spread out in the garden, but in the frying pan.
And, and, and, and...
The hidden gem point.
The hidden gem comes out from the side!
Here we go!
Double it.
What?
That's right.
What's this?
You're both big SDGs stakeholders.
Big stakeholders.
I'm an ambassador for DBS.
A very influential person
So we're going to use the pattern from the dashi pack this time.
Are you sure you've already used these?
Yes, these are the ones used for miso soup and so on.
Let them dry to a certain extent.
Add it here
Add it.
I'll add it.
I'm going to add it.
That's good.
Soy sauce.
And then soy sauce and mirin.And then season with soy sauce and mirin.
Really just a minute or two.
until all the water is absorbed.
Yes, sir.
Pour it over hot rice.
It's done.
Let's get nourished, Grandma.
No, no, no. Wait a minute.
That's it, that's it, that's it. Wait a minute.
I wrote the title at the start.
Say it again. Say it again.
The title is “Nourish your body with good health.
That's what I meant.
Shut up, Grandma.
Nourish yourself, Grandma. I forgot.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
It's wrapped in furikake. - That's so cool.
The dried bonito flakes are fragrant, but...
It's complicated. Bon appétit.
It's heavy.
I can taste the bonito more and more.
It's delicious.
My favorite.
Me too.
What's wrong? Is it hot?
It's good.
Is it hot? Now.
Sometimes I like the crunch of the almonds.
Delicious.
It's amazing what you can do in a fight like this.
You're good.
It's so good!
I'd buy them if they were on sale.
Next, what's the only treasure Kaki brought?And the only treasure Kaki brought next?
Beef tongue in chazuke with raayu soup.
What is it?
It looks delicious.
I love rice.
And I like ochazuke very much.
Why the beef tongue oil?
I'm sure you've all had it.
In Sendai...
At the concert.
That's right.
We get it every time.
I see.
I thought of the best way to eat it.
It looks delicious.
Yes, please.
Let's go to the kitchen studio, Mr. Himura.
Himura-san.
No, no, no.
There's no use for beef tongue.
Yes, there is.
It finally came today.
I didn't think oysters liked rice so much.
I like it.
I like white rice.
Really?
You like it?
Yes, I do.
But you've turned your back on it.
That's right.
I turn my back to everyone.
He makes rice balls and eats them.
What's so funny?
What's funny?
I don't know.
I don't know.I don't know.
I think it's a late-night meal.
That's why I wanted to eat it right away.
Speed.
So I don't use the knife anymore.
And I won't use that frying pan.
What?
I won't use anything.
I won't use it.
No more frying pans, no more knives.
I see.
Even if you're not a good cook.
I know, right?
Please open it.
Wait a minute, it's cute!
It won't open.
It won't open, maybe because I'm wearing gloves.
Open, open, open, open!
It's open, it's open, it's open.
But, Mr. Himura, you wanted to open it.
That was the time to do it, wasn't it?
Mr. Himura, put this down already.
I thought you'd show him.
That's right.
It's all greasy now.
Please open it.
Sure.
Slippery Slippery Slippery Slippery Slippery Slippery Slippery Slippery Slippery Slippery
It's so slimy!
It's too wet!
How long do you think it will last?
Eel
It's very slippery
Very slimy!
Put a little bit of beef tongue oil on the hot rice.
I've never had this before.
Is it spicy?
There is also a spicy version.Some of these are dry.
Then this one is like that.
This one maybe not so much.
It's like eating raayu, isn't it?
It's a little bit.
There are spicy ones, too.
Yes, I do.
It's just
Confidence is bad
What's this?
It's green onion.
And I sprinkled chopped green onions I bought at the supermarket.
Yes, it's soup ochazuke, isn't it?
So I'll make consomme soup.
I see.
I'll make consomme soup.
But usually I just pour this consommé on top and pour hot water over it.
But today is a bit special, so here it is.
Today, I'm making soup in a pot.
Why do you do this?
Why do you choose consommé out of all the soup stocks?
Because I had it at home.
I see.
Let's do it.
Yes, I'll put it in.
That makes sense.
I thought maybe you were going to use Japanese soup stock or something.
I found some at home and put it in, and it was delicious.
This goes well with it.
Shake, shake, shake, shake, shake, shake!
Listen to me for a second!
Shake, shake, shake, shake, shake!
Shake, shake, shake, shake!
Boogie moon abaloneBoogie Moon Abalone
Baby Baby Psycho
Hippie Hap Shake
Wáál
Jen
It's done!
Finished!
Put this on
It looks like this.
The smell of consommé is amazing!
The more you mix it, the more color it gets
That's right.
Bon appétit!
Wow, this is
This is delicious!
Like that tail soup.
But spicy.
It's true.
It's like tail soup.
That's what I thought at first, but it's spicy.
It's really good.
Oh, my God, that's good.
It's a dish in itself.
I had the consommé and the thin consommé.
But I keep adding more and more!
The thick consommé is better!
It's delicious.
It's richer?
What about the others?
I like spicy food.
It's delicious.
Tamura
I've always thought that I'm not a good cook.
I know.
Even when I did it before.
I was making weird things.
Don't say weird things.Don't be ridiculous.
This is good.
If Kakkiri can make it, so can I.
All you have to do is pour it on.
Anyone can make it.
Next, Kawasaki, who is an unknown cook, makes a rice dish.
Kimchi Chahan, Ishiyaki Bibimbap, and so on!
I see.
What?
It looks so good!
Oh, man.
Are you going to make something elaborate?
Yes, I do.
Yes, it is. - That's not bad at all.
Really?
No garnish.
What?
It's just stir-fry. It's quick and easy.
But it has to have some or else it's just kimchi?
No kimchi.
What?
You said kimchi.
I don't put it in.
Shota Himura will be on tonight.
Mr. Himura, Mr. Himura in the kitchen studio.
Here he comes.
What did you just put in?
I just added sesame oil.
The key is to start very low.
Weak at first.
Why is that?
I really like the charred bibimbap.
So I put it on very low at first.
Now the rice is ready!
Put the rice in a frying pan with sesame oil
Heat slowly over low heat
I'm a big believer in yakiniku sauce, kimchi sauce, and chicken stock.
I don't put in anything specific, really.I don't put in anything specific, really.
When it's lunch or something, I'll put in some namul or kimchi.
but at night, it's a real pain in the ass.
I want you to put in kimchi and namul.
You want to put that in?
Lunch version?
I'd like to try the lunch version.
I'd like to try it without it, but sure.
Finally, I'm going to add today's main dish.
What's this?
This is kimchi stock.
Kimchi stock.
You always have this with you?
I always keep some at home.
Do you cook a lot?
Not at all.
You look like you do.
How was the show?
The show was a lot of fun.
The stage is fun for everyone.
That's what it's like.
Thanks to the stage, my voice got louder.
You say the stage has made your voice louder.
That's true.
So you want to try the voice contest with Mr. Himura?
Let's try it.
What word would be loudest?
Power make-up.
What?
It's a stage.
That's a line.
Venus power make-up.
There's another one.
I didn't write it down.
Venus.
I play Venus.Venus role
Venus Power Makeup
Seiler Venus
Saylor Venus
Eh?
Saylor Venus.
What's the right word?
Laughter.
Oh, my God, he's playing with me.
Okay, let's start with Kawasaki, please.
OK.
Venus power makeover.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
You can speak louder.
That's great.
Okay, Mr. Himura, put your heart into it.
Sailor Venus.
Here we go.
Here we go!
Venus power make-up!
Laughter
Oh no, Uncle Dan.
Uncle
Transformer
Laughter
Kawasaki, you're not ready yet.
I didn't have enough training.
Laughs
Once the seasonings are blended, you add more yakiniku sauce.
And now it's time to start grilling.
This is now aoyaki time!
Aoyaki time
I'm making char
Yes, now...
Bake, bake, bake!
Bake time!Baking Time
Blame it on the hot summer
Laughter
You and no one else
You're so cute
It's so sweet
Laughter
I want to cut my parents off.
It's beach time.
It's beach time. I made a mistake.
Beach time.
I want to cut you off, I want to cut you off, I want to cut you off.
Hold me so tight, so tight, so tight.
I like beach time.
No, it's beach time.
Beach time.
Oh, my God, is it done?
Put some sesame oil around it.
I put a little more sesame oil on top and fry it up some more.
It's easier to remove.
I'm going to flip it over.
I'm going to turn it over now.
I'm going to flip it over now.
I can do it.
Just right, just right, just right.
I'm going to turn it over.
Be careful.
Here we go.
It's hot.
Come on.
That's him.
Oh, man.
Looks good!
Burnt rice!
It's done.
Looks good!Looks so good!
Bon appétit!
It's nice.
It's like a dinosaur's back.
Gobble, gobble, gobble.
It smells so good.
It's got kimchi, sesame oil, and yakiniku sauce.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Yum!
Yeah, it's like that.
This is getting better.
It's getting better, it's getting better, it's getting better.
The texture has changed.
This looks delicious!
I thought I knew what it tasted like, but it's even better than I imagined!
It's so good!
I love this okogane!
I'm sure it would be delicious with ochazuke, too!
I see.
It's really good!
So good!
The last in the rice dish category is Umezawa, who is going for two pieces!
I'm going to make rice mixed with minced chicken.
Looks so good!
This one has a lot of points, too.
But as long as you have a rice cooker, the rest is easy to do, so I recommend it!
Minced chicken?
Yes, I put minced chicken and kombucha in the rice cooker and cook it.
What? It's already cooked?
It really doesn't look that good right now.
Oh, wow.
Kitchen Studio, Mr. Imura.
Yes, yes.Yes, yes, yes.
The snack champion is back!
The snack champion has put down the rice this time.
What do you think, Champion?
I think the rice is not cooked properly.
What? It's not cooked at all.
Maybe it's not cooked at all.
I didn't put the rice on.
Umezawa was absolutely desperate because the rice he had prepared in advance was not cooked due to a mistake by the staff.
But worst case scenario, if there is regular rice, I'll fry some meat, add kombucha (kelp tea), and change it a bit in a hurry.
Feel the spiciness of rice
After this, a small restaurant Umezawa, recovery of the threat?
In fact, I cook minced chicken and kelp tea together, and put seasonings in it and mix them.
But today, I mix minced chicken stir-fried with kelp tea.
I see.
I'll put it in here.
Chicken minced with kelp tea?
Kelp tea is delicious.
I put the dashi soy sauce from Kamata that came out a while ago.
Ume plum is very Japanese.
A little bit.
What kind of soy sauce?
Dashi Shoyu from Kamata.
And Rokusuke salt.
There's all kinds.
There are all kinds of swamp salt.
It's a very famous salt.
It's delicious!
It tastes good with this, too.
It's not just salt?
It's a flavorful salt with kelp, dried shiitake mushrooms, dried scallops, and so on.
It's a flavorful salt with kelp, dried shiitake mushrooms, dried scallops, and other such ingredients.
This is it!
If you put this in, it's really bad.
It's not too salty.
Do you also make this?
Yes, I make this too.
All I have to do is cook the rice and mix it.I just cook the rice and mix it already.
You really do cook something, don't you?
Do you wear an apron at home?
I wear an apron.
I tend to spill a lot.
You tend to spill?
At home.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Spill it?
I tend to spill it.
I'm just, uh...
We're running out of time.
Mr. Himura stopped going over there.
I'm done.
He's the one doing it.
Add sesame seeds and shiso leaves.
Mix lightly.
Yes, sir.
by H.
It's a bit... colorful. It's very colorful.
Is it good? It's good.
Is it ready? I always eat these as onigiri.
Onigiri?
Very clever. Very clever.
You've been married a long time.
Single for six years? Very single.
I thought you were married with two kids. No, I'm still an idol.
Finally, rice balls... and it's done.
This late at night, it's not good. It's done.
Here it is. I gave it to him.
It looks so nice... with a stylish Japanese touch.
It really is stylish!
The shiso leaves and the aroma of freshly cooked rice.
It's delicious! Shiso leaves do such a good job!
Bon appétit! -Bon appétit! -Bon appétit!
It's good, it's good, it's salty, it's good, it's good.
This is so good!
This is too good!I don't know what the heck this is, it's good everywhere.
But the key to this is really the salt.
This is no ordinary salt.
You have to use Roxke's salt to get this flavor.
It's very good in the Ori-Giri market!
It's really good!
Oh my God!
It's too good!
Thank you so much!
The rice dishes section is also full of excellent products!
The one that won the daikon line and was chosen as the “Rice Terrorism Queen” was...
It was really good!
Seino
Ume!
You're really good at umeboshi!
I'm so happy!
That's great, Ume... two championships!
I'm so happy.
I'll make it anytime.
No way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll always make it.
That's good.
It's good.
No, even Mr. Himura, they were all good.
Everyone was good in the snacks category, too.
No, this is too high.
It's too high.
I think all the fans are making this now.
I wonder if they're making this scene now.
You're not making it now?
But don't copy it.
I think a lot of people are going to copy it.
I think it would be fun to do this in a different category.
I like it.
Tickets are now on sale to watch the live streaming of “Under Live”!
Enjoy!Enjoy!
Hello! My name is Mayu Tamura!
I have recently become addicted to eating asain and yogurt for lunch!
I hope you all try it too!
So please subscribe to my channel!
Bye bye!